<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Barbara Denney</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/introduction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Barbara Denney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.148.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:45:49 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating a brands within a design system</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/themableds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:45:49 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/themableds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CMS Design System&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once the Medicare design system was established, Ad Hoc was able to expand the current CMS Design System contract and &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the Medicare design system, Medicare decided to commit more time and money to the design system and expanded their contract to allow a Designer to work on the Medicare Design System full-time. I was already working on the design system part-time and was able to transfer over to the design system team and work on the design system full-time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Establishing a new Design System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/newds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:45:49 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/newds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medicare Design System&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Government contracting, in general, can pose many unique challenges regarding communication and alignment when building a product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication silos.&lt;/strong&gt; Due to multiple contractors working on the same website, communication silos are inevitable. Contracting teams are not incentivized to share information due to the focus on contract rebids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Onboarding overhead.&lt;/strong&gt; Many contracts are set up to be rebid every few years. Sometimes the contractor wins the rebid, but sometimes a new contractor wins. This causes whole parts of the product to change hands. Everyone from managers to engineers leaves the product, and another team moves in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Portfolio!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:45:49 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;welcome-to-my-portfolio&#34;&gt;Welcome to My Portfolio!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Barb Denney, I&amp;rsquo;m a Designer that specializes in Design Systems. I have 5 years of experienced in creating scalable, compliant Design Systems for Medicare.gov, CMS.gov, and VA.gov. I work in Figma and code. I started my career as a Web Designer almost 20 years ago, moved into UX, and now am starting era of my career exploring AI and Design Systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-youll-find-here&#34;&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Find Here&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This portfolio showcases my work, thoughts, and journey as a developer. You&amp;rsquo;ll find:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
